Mom on deck! Ten... Ho!
All right, grunts, here's
your pre-mission pep talk.
Shoot anyone
who doesn't obey hard enough.
But...
Stop gaining knowledge,
Hubert.
Lt's a simple mission.
The grunts catch the alien,
the surgeon guts it,
and you smuggle the
poison parts back here.
Uh, something
about poison, got it.
By the way,
that surgeon, where is he?
You! Where's the butcher?
Ma'am, I don't know, ma'am.
His duffel bag arrlved.
Lt's not a duffel bag.
It's my apartment!
Hubert, meet John Zoidberg.
You need an alien hacked to
pieces, he's the best there is,
in the budget category.
Have you ever
dissected a Yeti before?
Himalayan or Neptunian?
Tritonian.
A Tritonian Yeti?
You two aren't up to
anything unethical, are you?
Relax.
There's nothing unethical about
covert biological weapons research.
I said, "Relax!"
Ooh!
Ah, Zoidberg, we've known each
other so long that sometimes
I don't think we even need
words to understand each other.
What?
Once and for all, Fry,
even though it's the future, most
objects are still just objects,
not aliens who
look like objects.
So my efforts to establish
diplomatic relations
with the Cactus People
were doomed from the start.
So you're in pain and
have a bunch of needles?
I prescribe acupuncture.
Let's begin.
Blood?
I mean, blood.
Put it back in me!
I'm afraid Fry
lost a lot of juice.
He's developed
Simpsons Jaundice.
Ay, caramba!
His only hope is
some replacement liver.
Yours looks like
a good match.
Well, if it'll help Fry...
Careful, Leela! He knows less
about human anatomy than I do.
And I can't even
find my own uterus.
You may feel
a slight sawing.
And all we need is
a little spine supplement
to replace what Leela lost in
that unavoidable saw mix-up.
It wasn't unavoidable.
You just had to stop cutting
my spine when I yelled,
"Stop, you're cutting
my spine!"
Quit complaining!
My body rejected your liver, and
now I've got Garfield Syndrome.
Oh, I hate Mondays.
Anyhow, Hermes, all Leela
needs is one of your vertebrae.
But, Doctor, will I be
able to limbo afterwards?
Could you limbo before?
Wait. I say, "Yes," and you
say, "I couldn't limbo before."
You ruined the joke,
Hermes.
There you go, Leela.
Good as new!
Whoa! Whoa!
Oh. Sure,
Leela's fine,
but my jaundice has
progressed to Muppet Gangrene!
Lt's not easy
being gangrenous.
I thought you were only gonna
take out one vertebra!
Yeah, but did you ever
play Jenga?
Sometimes you pull one and...
Yeah, well, I'm not staying like this.
I can't believe it.
Mmm. What started out as a pleasant
afternoon of drugs and surgery
has not gone as planned.
But don't worry,
we still have three or four
co-workers with plenty of spare parts.
My first mission.
I'm so excited.
And after I dissect
the Yeti's poison glands,
we can stop, maybe, for
ice cream on the way back?
With sprinkles on?
Why, you're just a big
kid, aren't you, Zoidberg?
A very big kid!
We're over the drop zone, gentlemen.
Might I suggest you jump out
the door and poop yourselves?
Aah!
So anyway, I hope the men have been
taking their hyper-malaria pills.
Their what?
"Their what?"
That's funny,
like a crazy old man.
But you know
what's not funny?
Deadly Tritonian
hyper-malaria.
Just be sure to stay out
of the methane swamps.
What smells like methane?
My God! I've never seen
such a gruesome shark attack.
Especially
this far inland.
It wasn't a shark. It was
an awful, incompetent doctor.
Wow, he must've been
a total Zoidberg.
It was Zoidberg!
He brutalized us with power
tools, gypsy curses and hypnosis.
Yes, master.
You'll all get through this. I
give you my word as a real doctor.
What about me?
What did he do to you?
I don't know exactly,
but I'm incontinent.
I'm truly sorry.
I consider myself
a reasonable man.
Quick with a joke,
slow to anger.
But Bender can't go on
long car trips anymore,
and I say Zoidberg must die.
People, please.
Let's not overreact...
Death to the crab!
How bad is it,
Doctor?
Super bad. It's
Tritonian hyper-malaria.
A lot of these men will
be dead within 24 hours.
What?
Not you, though.
You'll make
a complete recovery
and go on to
marry a supermodel!
Funny plague,
hyper-malaria.
It can kill immediately,
or lie dormant for decades.
But sooner or later,
it erupts,
causing fever, spasms, madness,
coma, and finally death.
What?
Supermodel!
Oh! Those poor,
doomed bastards.
I guess it's up to me
to complete the mission.
I'll be in the swamp, blowing
the smirk off a toxic Yeti.
Professor, we need
to talk, man-to-mob.
We've had it with Zoidberg!
We demand you fire him!
Nonsense. Zoidberg's a
fine physician, for aliens.
Your mistake
is being humans.
No, if I'm going to fire
anyone, it'll be Scruffy.
You can't do that.
Over my dead body!
Don't you get it,
old man?
Thanks to Dr. Scissorhands, I
wet myself every time I laugh.
Lt's not funny!
Well, I guess it is
kind of funny.
Oh-oh.
Why are you protecting
Zoidberg, Professor?
Do you owe him
something?
Is he blackmailing you somehow?
What does he have
on you?
Why have you kept him around
all these years
when he's so grossly
incompetent?
Long ago, Zoidberg and I
entered into a secret arrangement
relating to certain extraordinary
events too horrible to reveal.
So there's nothing
to be curious about.
Oh!
Stop, or I'll shoot!
Zoidberg?
You can't hunt a Yeti by
yourself, sir. It's suicidal!
So what? I'm going to die
of hyper-malaria, anyway.
I was in the same swamp
as the rest of the men.
Just because you were in the
swamp doesn't necessarily mean...
I was thirsty from the
flight. I drank swamp water.
Look, Zoidberg,
you're a loyal friend.
"Friend"?
But I'm doomed!
I might as well capture a Yeti
and die trying.
Then you'll need someone
to dissect it, friend.
Go, Johnny! Go!
That's an order!
Never! Zoidberg doesn't
abandon a friend, apparently.
I'll save us by scaring him
off with my crazy war noise.
Crunch all you want.
I'll make more.
Oy. I lost another one.
Zoidberg, I'm sorry to
break it to you this way,
but we hate you and we
never wanna see you again.
But, friends...
We're not your friends!
We're your victims!
I was just
trying to...
Shut up and give me
my kidney back!
I'm sorry.
We don't know why the
Professor keeps you around here,
and we don't care.
You're a terrible doctor!
Nobody wants to
see you ever again!
Dr. Zoidberg! I want
to see you right now!
The time
has come, my friend.
We have to talk
about our arrangement.
Oh, no. No, no.
Oh, no, no, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no!
Un-paw him,
you big ape!
I saw this in a Tarzan movie!
Lt was called
Tarzan versus the Yetis.
I lost my virginity
during the film,
so I'm a little fuzzy
on the details.
Oh!
John, are you all right?
You...
You saved my life!
Oh, fuff.
Yes, fuff.
How can I ever
repay you?
Do you need a slave?
Or maybe a butler?
No, I haven't needed a butler
since grad school.
But I do need a doctor.
I don't want to die
like those Marines, John.
The fever, the madness.
Don't forget the spasms,
coma and death.
Oh. I don't want to go through
that. I want you to kill me.
All right.
Give me the knife.
Not now! Hyper-malaria
can lie dormant for years.
Isn't that what you said?
Lt sounds like
something I would say.
So stay with me
until the symptoms start,
then put me
out of my misery.
You must swear!
All right, Hubert,
I swear.
It's started, Zoidberg, the
fever, the muscle spasms.
I'm dying.
Lt's time for you to keep
your promise and kill me.
This is very difficult,
but I'll try, friend.
No, wait,
I'm afraid to die.
Ah. You said
you wanted me to kill you.
Is this one of those
"no means yes" deals?
Yes and no.
I do want you to kill me,
but I mustn't see it coming.
That would be agony.
So you must murder me
completely by surprise.
As God is my witness,
you can count on me.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Not surprising enough.
Oh. Ah!
My heart!
Ho.
Hey.
What are you doing there?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Stop, you don't
understand.
Let's go, you murderer.
Fry, help me lock him up.
Hang on. I'm learning
how to do loop-de-loops.
Whoa, whoa!
You're making a mistake. I was
only trying to kill the Professor.
Hubert, I'm sorry.
Huh? He doesn't have hair.
Great Little Caesar's ghost!
You fools, you stupid,
life-prolonging fools.
I asked Zoidberg
to kill me.
What you talking about, Professor? What?
Professor, have you gone mad?
Probably. It's one of the symptoms
of Tritonian hyper-malaria.
You mean the incurable
disease that causes fever,
spasms, insanity,
Coma,
And finally death?
Yes, and I begged Zoidberg
to put me out of my misery.
Bring him, quickly.
Should have known better than to
store my antiques in the office.
Zoidberg,
we were wrong.
We're letting you out so
you can kill the Professor.
No, he sand-crabbed out.
Then we
have no choice.
We'll have to mercy-kill
the Professor ourselves.
Well, let's get started.
We have a situation, Mother.
This creature tried to
sand-crab into the building.
Zoidberg?
Sorry I didn't call first,
Carol, but I'm in a hurry.
I need your help
to save Hubert.
Let him go and stooge
the hell out of here.
We're on it.
Beautiful kids.
You must be very proud.
John Zoidberg. It's been a
long time. How have you been?
Not too bad.
Last year I took a bus trip
to the Grand Canyon.
Later, I'll show you
the pictures.
Do you ever regret it, John,
leaving me to work for the Professor?
Oh...
What do you want me to say?
He saved my life.
Big deal. You could have
been rich if you'd stayed.
Your own lab,
a full staff.
But Hubert is my friend.
He's very sick.
I can cure him, but I need the
thing, the thing from Triton.
It'll cost you, John.
How much are you worth now?
I live in a dumpster.
All I have in the world
is this coupon
for one free session
at the tanning salon.
Oh, John, that's really all you have?
Then, I'll take it.
Okay, Murdolator's finished.
I said I'd kill him myself,
but nobody listens to Bender.
We all have to
share in the guilt,
which is why we're each going to add
one drop of cyanide to the death wheel
as it goes by.
Commence mercy-killing
in three, two, a-yup.
Kill-check one is go.
Kill-check two is go.
Ooh!
Lt's about time.
Vegetables activated.
Kill-check three is go.
Also, the salad's ready.
Yes!
Salad!
What the hell are you doing?
Zoidberg, we know about
your secret agreement.
I am so, so sorry
for how we treated you.
And to make it up to you, we're
killing the Professor for you
so he doesn't die horribly
from hyper-malaria.
He doesn't have hyper-malaria,
you idiots.
He has Yeti-ism.
When he saved my life
all those years ago,
he was scratched
by a Yeti.
Hmm. I consider myself almost
completely ignorant of modern medicine,
and I've never
heard of Yeti-ism.
It mimics the symptoms
of hyper-malaria exactly
except for the part where instead
of dying, you turn into a Yeti.
Ah!
Wow. Hold him down while
I prepare the antidote.
Another Yeti?
Yes, the same jerk that once
noshed on me like a shrimp toast.
Now who's getting
his pineal gland extracted?
Yes, this contains a concentrated
form of the Yeti neurotoxin.
But that's what gave him
Yeti-ism in the first place.
Won't it just make him
a double-Yeti?
Don't lecture me about
allen physiology, Conrad.
The pineal neurotoxin neutralizes
the adrenal neurotoxin.
That's why Yetis don't
drive themselves mad.
My God, he's like some kind
of believable Hulk.
No time for an injection.
Ah!
I'll be damned.
It did make him a double-Yeti.
Lt wasn't supposed to do
any of those things.
You did it, Johnny.
I'm cured!
All right, let's set
it up and try again.
There's one thing
I don't understand, Zoidberg.
How did you persuade Mom to
give you her precious Yeti head?
Did you have to
promise anything in return?
Nothing, nothing at all.
This calls for a celebration. Come
on, everyone, let's go tanning.
Hurray!
I was going to tan once.
What do you say, Johnny?
Lt's on me.
Thank you, Hubert.